yoraps.com 2010-06-03

# YO! RAPS MAGAZINE | HIPHOP & R&B 24/7 - ANYTIME, ANYWHERE | WWW.YORAPS.COM

|   
---  
  
---|---  
---  
| 

[** |   
---  
**](http://www.djbijal.com/)[](http://www.bestbuy.com/site/olspage.jsp;jsessionid=I1X1EBZSSCIZVKC4D3FVAGY?_dyncharset=ISO-8859-1&id=pcat17071&type=page&st=gorilla+Zoe&sc=Global&cp=1&nrp=15&sp=&qp=&list=n&iht=y&usc=All+Categories&ks=960)

|   
---  
  
We respect the privacy of our newsletter subscribers, customers, contacts, those who answer our surveys, and those who fill out our questionnaires. It is our policy: 

  1. **Choice and Consent:** To respect the purpose for which our site visitors gave us information. We give users choice and consent over how their personal information is used, and remove names immediately upon request.   

  2. **Third Party Use:** To not sell, rent, or loan our subscriber or customer lists to third parties for e-mail marketing. While we sell advertising in our e-mail publications to other companies, we never allow third parties any other use of these subscriber lists.   

  3. **Unsubscriptions:** To send our periodicals only to those who request them (that is, opt-in). We immediately unsubscribe those who request it through convenient unsubscribe links in every e-mailing. Our welcome message to subscribers and every issue of our newsletters/e-zine's clearly explain how to unsubscribe. We keep our subscription lists as clean as possible to prevent obsolete e-mail addresses which use unnecessary bandwidth.   

  4. **Cookies:** To use cookies in a responsible manner to help our visitors, not snoop on them. We use cookies to: (a) to help rotate banner advertising; (b) to identify shoppers with their shopping carts; (c) to make it easy to order a second time; (d) to allow subscribers to store passwords in cookies if they desire; and (e) to give proper credit for sales made through links on our affiliates' sites. We do not collect or use information from cookies to develop a profile about our visitors or shoppers.   

  5. **Security:** To store subscriber and password files with personal information in a secure manner. We store such files in areas not accessible to Web browsers, behind password protection, or off-line.   

  6. **Termination:** To continue this policy beyond the termination of our company. If a majority portion of the assets of our company were to be acquired by another organization, that might include our subscriber and other lists, but only as part of a clear agreement binding that organization to abide by the spirit and letter of our privacy policy. 

Your use of Yoraps.com is expressly conditioned on your acceptance of and agreement to this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy sets forth the terms and conditions that apply to your use of Yoraps.com. By using Yoraps.com , you agree to abide by this Privacy Policy. 

If you have any concerns or questions about our privacy policy or information collected on our sites, please [**contact us**](mailto:info@yoraps.com?subject=Privacy%20Policy).  
  
Yo! Raps takes no responsibility or liability for any errors or inaccuracies on any page of the Yo! Raps site. 

We endeavor to provide accurate information relating to each link provided (including those linked to from text, banner or button advertisements), but as linked sites are regularly updated we cannot accept responsibility for inaccurate descriptions or any of their content. 

Any logos or other copyrighted material used within the site are for the purpose of providing the end-user with relevant information and are not considered to be the intellectual property of Yo! Raps. If you are the copyright holder of any material used and would like it removed, email us with the details.   
  
|   
---  

| **Kaleena - It's Dirty Money**  
---  
  
[_Last_ _Train To Paris_ is not only the upcoming sixth studio opus from producer/rapper/actor/fashion designer/entrepreneur, **Sean "Diddy" Combs** , but, maybe even more important than that, it also features his newfound collective, **Dirty Money** , comprised of himself, **Dawn Richard** , formerly of **Danity Kane** , and uber talented singer/songwriter, **Kaleena**... **[Read More]**](https://web.archive.org/web/20100603052834id_/http%3A//www.yoraps.com/features1.php?subaction=showfull&id=1274948433&archive=&start_from=&ucat=3&)  

**

**  
  
  |    
  
|   
  
---
